Brittany Fortner

1055 W Baseline Rd Apt 1093, Mesa, AZ 85210 • 719-243-8685 • brittany.e.fortner@gmail.com

Summary

Front-End Web Developer passionate about building elegantly functional responsive websites and user interfaces. Earning a Full Stack Development Certificate through the University of Arizona to sharpen my proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and mySLQ. Effective working individually and on a team, with extensive experience in meeting deadlines with quality work. Exceptional organizational skills and attention to detail help me create intuitive designs to better serve end-users. Excited to use these programming and structural skills in future as a strong addition to a forward-thinking team of web developers.

Bilingual: English/Spanish.

Highlights

- Proven customer service skills
- Excellent time management skills
- Exceptional interpersonal skills

- Creative and critical thinker
- Strong work ethic
- · Extremely quick learner

Experience

Veritas Management Group – The Centers at Val Vista, Arrowhead & Tucson - Gilbert, AZ Regional Billing Director July 2018 – December 2019

Business Office Manager - Val Vista

February 2017 – June 2018

- Cash collections 2019 averaged 101.6% for established facilities, 96.3% for new facility
- Billed Medicare, Medicaid, and commercial insurance for all three facilities
- Managed receptionists, trained business office assistants
- Positively interacted with hundreds of patients in regard to finances and facility stay

Osborn Health and Rehabilitation – Scottsdale, AZ

Assistant Business Office Manager

October 2015 – February 2017

- Averaged 100.29% cash collections in private collections category for 2016
- Managed nursing staffing while continuing all business office duties
- Responsible for all Medicaid and private billing and collections

Casa Hogar Providencia – Navojoa, Sonora, Mexico

Orphanage Director

April 2014 – October 2015

Lead House Mother

September 2007 – September 2011

- Motivated and managed caregivers, providing training, conflict resolution, and support
- Represented and promoted orphanage locally and internationally
- Established professional relationship with DIF (Social Services) for orphanage

Education

University of Arizona

Full-Stack Web Development Certification candidate - anticipated completion April 2020

Instituto Bautista Providencia

Bachelor of Religious Studies